http://quickpractice.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Want to know more?
Download a Free TrialWant an Online Demo?Request a call backCall 800.676.3279
Who uses QuickPractice?ChiropractorsMedical DoctorsPhysical TherapistsMental HealthPodiatristsBilling Companies
Partners
ProductsSummaryStandardDeluxeProfessionalE-DocsFeaturesServicesElectronic ServicesSupport & TrainingOther ServicesPricingFAQTestimonialsBilling CompaniesChiropractorsMedical DoctorsMental Health SpecialistsPhysical TherapistsPodiatristsWhy QP?Why QP?
QuickPractice > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Following is the PracticePRO Software Systems® Web Site Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using this site.
Overview
Privacy is important to PracticePRO
Software Systems Incorporated (” PracticePRO
Software Systems”), a responsible participant in the healthcare industry. PracticePRO
Software System’s corporate policy is to protect the privacy and confidentiality of our customers and those individuals whose healthcare information may be identified within the transaction data services supplied by PracticePRO
Software Systems to our customers. This Privacy Policy describes what information PracticePRO
Software Systems collects and how that information is protected and used.
Privacy Principles
PracticePRO Software Systems operates under the following set of strict privacy principles:
The only information PracticePRO
Software Systems obtains about an individual visitor to its web site is information supplied voluntarily by that visitor.
Information supplied by a visitor that could be used to identify or contact that visitor, such as name, e-mail address or other similar information (“Personal Information”), will not be disclosed to anyone unless the visitor indicates that PracticePRO
Software Systems may do so.
PracticePRO Medical Record Software Systems may share statistical information about its visitors as a group, such as usage habits, demographics and similar information that cannot be used to identify or contact visitors (“Aggregate Information”), with any partner of PracticePRO
Software Systems. However, PracticePRO
Software Systems will not share Personal Information about a visitor at any time without the visitor’s permission. Personal Information about an individual contained within e-health transactions, reports and other summaries derived from e-health transactions, or within administrative information necessary to conduct e-health transactions, that can be used to identify or contact that individual will be protected by PracticePRO
Software Systems as “Individually Identifiable Health Information” in accordance with the requirements and definitions of the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act ( HIPAA) of 1996 (Public Law 104-191) and any implementing regulations.
PracticePRO
Software Systems will also observe all other state and federal laws relating to transmission, storage, and access to medical records and other healthcare data.
The following describes our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site:
Disclosure of Personal Information
Except as set forth herein, PracticePRO Software Systems will not disclose to unaffiliated companies any Personal Information about our visitors and customers. Any Personal Information provided to entities affiliated with PracticePRO
Software Systems will be treated in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Except as set forth in this document, PracticePRO
Software Systems will not disclose to unaffiliated companies any Personal Information contained within payment processing or e-health transactions. Any Personal Information provided to entities affiliated with PracticePRO
Software Systems will be treated in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. PracticePRO
Software Systems will consider, and may release, Personal Information to third parties to comply with law or to protect the rights, property or safety of PracticePRO
Software Systems and our customers. PracticePRO
Software Systems may provide to third parties Aggregate Information that does not allow the individuals to be identified or contacted.
Registration
The PracticePRO Software Systems site requires visitors to register either before accessing the web site or as a requirement to access specific portions of the web site. Registration includes the collection of contact information such as visitor name and e-mail address.
IP Addresses
An IP address is a number assigned to your computer for accessing the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. PracticePRO
Software Systems collects IP addresses in order to conduct system administration, report aggregate information to sponsors and advertisers, and to conduct site analysis. If a visitor requests pages from the PracticePRO
Software Systems web site, the PracticePRO
Software Systems servers enter the visitor’s IP address into a log. To maintain visitor anonymity, PracticePRO
Software Systems does not associate IP addresses with records containing Personal Information. However, PracticePRO
Software Systems will use IP addresses to identify any visitors who refuse to comply with PracticePRO
Software Systems terms of service, and to identify visitors who threaten our service, site, or customers.
Cookies
The PracticePRO
Software Medical Billing Systems site may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. The PracticePRO
Software Systems site uses cookies during your online session to confirm that access to our site is authorized and to control certain parameters of your communication session with our site. Sponsors and advertisers may also use cookies if you select their advertisement; we are unable to control their use of cookies or how they manage the information they gather.
Payment Processing and E-Health Transactions
Some PracticePRO Software Systems site features may use applications to collect data to facilitate a payment processing or e-health transactions. We will obtain your explicit permission to transfer this data to the third party to facilitate this transaction as part of the transaction processing service agreement you voluntarily enter into with PracticePRO
Software Systems. PracticePRO Software Systems may store this information to verify the transaction for customer service and accounting reasons and may use this information to help personalize your experience on the PracticePRO Software Systems site. PracticePRO Medical Record Software Systems may also share this information with other third parties on an aggregate basis, but not in any manner that would permit the third party to identify or contact individual users of our site. PracticePRO Software Systems will maintain and protect “Individually Identifiable Health Information” that it receives in connection with e-health transactions in accordance with the requirements of the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) of 1996 (Public Law 104-191).
External Links
In order to provide visitors with greater value, PracticePRO
Software Systems may provide links to various third party web sites. However, even if a third-party affiliation exists between PracticePRO
Software Systems and that destination site, PracticePRO
Software Systems EXERCISES NO AUTHORITY OVER LINKED SITES, EACH OF WHICH MAINTAINS INDEPENDENT PRIVACY AND DATA COLLECTION POLICIES AND PROCEDURES. PracticePRO
Software Systems ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR THESE INDEPENDENT METHODS OR ACTIONS AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE INDEPENDENT POLICIES OR PROCEDURES OF DESTINATION SITES. SIMILARLY, PracticePRO
Software Systems CANNOT TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE PRIVACY INITIATIVES OR THE CONTENT OF SUCH WEB SITES. THESE DESTINATION LINKS ARE PROVIDED ONLY FOR YOUR CONVENIENCE, AND AS SUCH, YOU ACCESS THEM AT YOUR OWN RISK. However, PracticePRO
Software Systems wishes to protect the integrity of the PracticePRO
Software Systems web site and its destination links, so any comments pertaining to the PracticePRO
Software Systems web site or any sites accessed through PracticePRO
Software Systems links are greatly appreciated.
Security
PracticePRO Software Systems combines industry-standard technical safeguards with employee policies to help prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of Personal Information under our control. Only authorized PracticePRO
Software Systems employees, agents or independent contractors are permitted to access your Personal Information, and all such employees, agents and independent contractors must agree in writing to abide by PracticePRO Software Systems Privacy Policy. Those who violate the Privacy Policy are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. PracticePROMedical Record Software Systems employs strict security measures to safeguard online transactions; Personal Information is stored in secured systems and is always encrypted when sent via Internet channels. Despite these security measures, PracticePRO Software Systems DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WILL BE PROTECTED AGAINST LOSS, MISUSE OR ALTERATION BY THIRD PARTIES.
Online Service Agreement
Please see our Online Service Agreement for other terms and conditions governing your use of the PracticePRO
Software Systems web site.
Privacy Policy Changes
PracticePRO Software Systems may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to our web site. Your use of the site constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and your continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, then please exit the site immediately.
Questions
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this web site, or your interaction with this web site, contact: PracticePRO Software Systems 20 Jay Street, Ste 206, Brooklyn, NY 11201. Copyright © 2000-2010. PracticePRO Software Systems. All Rights Reserved
HomeSummaryStandardDeluxeProfessionalE-DocsFeaturesElectronic ServicesSupport & TrainingPricingFAQTestimonialsWhy QP?QP Change LogBilling CompaniesChiropractorsMedical DoctorsMental Health SpecialistsPhysical TherapistsPodiatrists Medical Office BillingElectronic Billing SoftwareMedical Management SoftwareChiropractic SoftwarePhysical Therapy SoftwareHealth Care Software
Privacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsSite MapContact
© 1995-2020 PracticePRO Software Systems Inc.
